<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Development on R at the Margin</title>
    <link>/categories/development/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Development on R at the Margin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automated Trading System</title>
      <link>/portfolio/automated-trading-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/automated-trading-system/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a R article written by Wei Lin. It is about using R to build data product to do long-term trading. It is a simple automated system in R that Wei Lin built while learning R. I am going to do the same. Content coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Make Something Shiny</title>
      <link>/portfolio/make-something-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/make-something-shiny/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the things that I would love to do is make Shiny apps. I will blog about my effort. The content is coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering R for Quantitative Finance</title>
      <link>/portfolio/mastering-r-for-quantitative-finance/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/mastering-r-for-quantitative-finance/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I am going to follow the writing of Edina Berlinger on using R to optimize trading strategy. Also, I am hoping to build up my risk management system. Content coming soon.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Reliable Trading Systems</title>
      <link>/portfolio/building-reliable-trading-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/building-reliable-trading-systems/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This book written by Keith Fitschen provides a lot of chart examples. I hope this can help me get used to reading charts and forming insights to action. This book will serve as perfect complement to other projects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trades About to Happen</title>
      <link>/portfolio/trades-about-to-happen/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/trades-about-to-happen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I hope Trades About to Happen can serve as a good complement to finding trades. Price and volume analysis is one of the most effective approaches to market analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Param Jeet - Learning quantitative finance with R</title>
      <link>/portfolio/param-jeet-learning-quantitative-finance-with-r/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/portfolio/param-jeet-learning-quantitative-finance-with-r/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Understand the basics of R and how they can be applied in various Quantitative Finance scenarios. I want to learn how to use R to build quantitative finance models with ease. content will follow.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title>
      <link>/post/goisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/goisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Hugo uses the excellent go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using go templates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started with Hugo</title>
      <link>/post/hugoisforlovers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hugoisforlovers/</guid>
      <description>Step 1. Install Hugo Goto hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your os and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at installing hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:
 Clone the hugo repository Go into the repo Run hugo in server mode and build the docs Open your browser to http://localhost:1313  Corresponding pseudo commands:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>